

eng Yuen F

PROGRAMMER · INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Flat 2, 14/F, Lai Chung House, Mei Chung Court, Tai Wai, Shatin, NT

🛘 (+852) 67386569 | 🔀 chengyuenpui1234@gmail.com | 🖸 kittychengyuenpui | **in** kitty-cheng-a20937171

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary.

Currently working as IT Programmer at CMA Testing. 4 years experience specializing in front-end and in-house web application development. Familiar with C#. Net and utilizing Microsoft Graph API on projects. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if needed.

Work Experience

CMA Testing (CMA Industrial Development Foundation Limited)

https://www.cmatesting.org/

SENIOR PROGRAMMER

INTERNSHIP

July 2019 - Now

- Develop, maintain and enhance in-house system applications and websites
- · Prepare system documentation, system support and troubleshooting on the developed systems
- Implemented several API microservices in written in .NET Core.
- Deployed a Document Sign Web Service (.asmx) with PKCS11Interop and SafeNet eToken (GlobalSign)
- Integrated with Microsoft Graph API for data connections

WWF (World Wide Fund for Nature Hong Kong)

https://www.wwf.org.hk/

Aug. 2018 - Mar. 2019

• Assisted in a blockchain project for sustainable fashion

· Built an online questionnaire with PHP code on 000WebHost for mobile devices to show different results after submission according to the answers chosen by a respondent

Star Fantasy https://www.starfantasy.net/

NTP XSport Helper (PART-TIME JOB)

Aug. 2015 - Sep. 2015

Provided relevant information for visitors and answered their questions with problem-solving skills

Education

The Hong Kong Polytechnic University

2.65 Award GPA

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (HONOURS) IN COMPUTING

ASSOCIATE OF ENGINEERING (COMPUTER SCIENCE)

Sep. 2016 - Aug. 2019

- · Studied courses related to Computer Science, database concepts, information systems knowledge
- Applied computing theories and programming methodologies in projects and assignments

HKUSPACE Community College

3.56 Graduation GPA

Sep. 2014 - Aug. 2016

- Studied courses related to the field of Computer Science, programming skills, logical thinking and problem-solving skills are learned
- Applied problem-solving skills in projects and assignments

Skills

Programming HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, C#, SQL, Python, Java

Back-end Django, REST API, .Net/.NET Core

Front-end React, HTML5, LESS

Framework and Tools Ant Design of React, Umi, Next.js

Computer Systems Windows and Linux

Languages Cantonese, English, and Mandarin

AUGUST 24, 2023 · RESUME ·